Guide to the Nate Brown Western Sound Archive Collection ARS.0124
Archive of Recorded Sound
- 10 prefix (10.5" reels)
  - 10-260. Weingartner, LSO. Berlioz, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 28)
  - 10-262. Wagner; Schumann; Bach; Brahms; Franck [78 discs], 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 28)
  - 10-263. Beecham, RPO. Delius, Romeo [HMV 78s], 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 28)
  - 10-265. Enesco, Orchestra Radio-Symphonique de Paris, Thibaud. Mozart K.216, K.218, K.219 [RTF 401 D 961, 962, 965], 1951-12-13; 3 open reel tapes 9" pancakes in metal tins (Audio 28)
  - 10-270. Horenstein, BBC Northern Orchestra, Hodgson, Mitchinson. Mahler, Das Lied, 1972; 1 open reel tapes (8.5" reel) (Audio 28)
  - 10-274. Furtwangler. RAI Rome 1/19/52; Berlin Philharmonic 6/20/50, 12/7/52; 5/14/54, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 28)
  - 10-278. Tennstedt, Cleveland Orchestra., Frager, Gutierrez. Blossom Music Center, 1975-07; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 28)
  - 10-280. Martinon, Hague Philharmonic. Saint-Saens, Mahler. Holland Festival, 1975-06-13; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 28)
  - 10-285. De Waart, Cleveland Orchestra, Chung, Firkusny, 1975-07; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 28)
  - 10-291. Stravinsky, Hungarian State Symphony, Budapest Chorus, 1963; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 28)
  - 10-324. Furtwangler, Vienna Philharmonic. Stockholm 9/25/50; Furtwangler, Stockholm Philharmonic 1948; Furtwangler, Vienna Philharmonic 5/29/53, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 28)
  - 10-324 (2). Walter, Paris Radio Orchestra. 5/12/55, 6/14/56; Furtwangler, Stockholm Philharmonic 11/25/42; Toscanini, NY Philharmonic 4/19/36, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 28)
  - 10-325. Walter, Paris Radio Orchestra 5/5/55; 5/12/55, 1955-05; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 28)
  - 10-326. Samuel, Oakland Symphony 1/18/77; Farberman, Oakland Symphony, Berman 3/15/77, Tobias 4/12/77, 1977; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 28)
  - 10-327. Mengelberg, Concertgebouw 3/28/40; 12/12/40; 11/26/39; 12/8/40; 5/23/36; 5/9/35; 10/9/38; 10/10/40, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 10-328. Adolph Busch, Violin. Wallenstein, WOR Orchestra 2/21/42; Munch, Basel Radio Orchestra 12/18/51; Zurich Recital 8/17/44, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 10-329. Walter, NBC Symphony. Mahler 4/18/39; 2/6/44, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 10-330. Walter, NY Philharmonic, Milstein 11/1/42; Barbirolli, Scarlatti Association Orchestra, Ciani 1/4/68; Bittner, Hamburg Radio Orchestra, Geiseking; Wallenstein, LA Philharmonic, Michelangeli 1/16/49, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 10-335. Da Sabata, New York Philharmonic. Barber, Schumann, Beethoven 3/18/51; Wagner 3/25/51, 1951-03; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 10-336. Rostropovich, Academy of St. Martins-In-The-Fields. Haydn, Cello Concertos in D Major, C Major. PBS 3/30/77; Farberman, Oakland Symphony, Arrau. Beethoven, Concerto No.4. 12/8/77, 1977; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 10-337. Szell. Cleveland Orchestra, Concertegouw Orchestra, Cologne Radio Symphony Orchestra, 1964-1967; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 10-345. De Sabata, New York Philharmonic. Rachmaninoff, Ravel 3/26/50; Sibelius 3/5/50, 1950-03; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 10-346. Walter, London Symphony 11/13/47; Walter, NY Philharmonic 1/18/48, 1947-1948; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 348. Furtwangler, Vienna Philharmonic. Mozart 2/8/49; 1/27/52, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 349. Walter, Stockholm Philharmonic. Mozart, Schubert 8/9/50; Dubs of Goldman Collection, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 356. Page, Cleveland Orchestra, Chorus. Vaughn Williams, Symphony No.1 4/18/74; Tennstedt, Cleveland Orchestra, Frager. Mozart, Piano Concerto No.16, K.451. 6/22/77, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 359. Slatkin, San Francisco Symphony. All Beethoven Program, 1979-06-22; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 361. Bruno Walter. WDR Memorial Broadcast; Hess Rundfunk Memorial Broadcast 2/18/72, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 364. Goldberg, Netherlands Chamber Orchestra. Bach. Aldeburgh Festival, 1960; 1 10.5" open reel tape folders (Audio 32)
  - 365A. Kirkpatrick Dub, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 365B. Kirkpatrick Dub, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 369. Furtwangler, BPO. Bruckner, Brahms, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 370. Furtwangler, BPO 5/1/51, 5/14/43; Furtwangler, RAI Torino 3/3/52; Rossi, RAI Turino, Michelangeli 12/23/55, 12/18/59, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 381. Klemperer, LA Philharmonic 12/16/45 [etc.], 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 382. De Waart, San Francisco Symphony, Stern 11/12/80; Mehta, New York Philharmonic, Stern, Zukerman, Perlman 9/24/80, 1980; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 384. De Waart, San Francisco Symphony. Berio, Mendellssohn, Mahler 10/1/80; Rossini, Ketting, Weber, Beethoven 10/8/80, 1980-10; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 389. Desormiere, Orchestre National de la RTF 6/7/51; Bohm, Orchestre de Paris 3/13/80; Inghelbrecht, Orchestre National de la RTF [etc.], 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 29)
  - 391. Giulini, Boston Symphony 3/2/62; 3/9/62, 1962-03; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 396. Bohm, Vienna Philharmonic, Pollini 8/17/77; Abbaolo, Vienna Philharmonic, Pollini. Vienna Festival 5/23/76, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 397. Klemperer. Heyworth, WDR. Zurich, 1970-11; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 408. Kabasta, Munich Philharmonic 1943; Stravinsky, NDR Symphony 1958; Blech, NDR Symphony 1951, 11/14/49; Mitropoulos, Cologne Radio Orchestra, Krasner 7/16/54, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 409. Tertis, Murdoch [L-1731]; Lambert, LPO (Vic 12764]; Ormandy, Minneapolis Symphony [Vic 14031] [etc.], 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 10-414. Hess [Columbia 2512-D]; Mahler, Erie Philhatmonic 1/21/50; Goosens, Cincinatti Symphony; Muck, Berlin State Opera Orchestra [M-67] [etc.], 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 417. Walter, New York Philharmonic. Bruckner, Symphony No.8, 1941-01-26; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 421. Walter, Vienna Philharmonic. Mozart, Mahler 5/18/52; Walter, NY Philharmonic. Beethoven 3/16/49 Haydn 12/12/48, Mozart 2/5/50, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 423. Cologne Radio Orchestra, Chorus. Reger, Hindemith 11/11/55; Monteux, Orchestra National de la RTF. Hindemith, Mozart 9/22/57, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 426. Vasary. Mozart, Concerto in A Major; Sopkin, Atlanta Symphony. Beethoven, Concerto No.2, Rachmaninoff, Rhapsody, 1962-1963; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 435. Paray, Israel Philharmonic. Prokofiev, Mozart, Saint-Saens, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 438. Boulez, Cleveland Orchestra. Liszt 1/14/71; Berlioz 7/13/71; Schubert 3/28/71; Ravel 7/17/69; Schubert 11/9/67, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 10-443. RPX 1892-1898, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 448. Michelangeli. Beethoven 4 and 5 [reels says Mahler II. BFA Orig.], 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 460. Michelangeli. Beethoven, Schubert, Scarlatti, Debussy 3/17/75; Ravel. Helsini 1969, Firenze 2/12/52; RAI. Chopin 1962, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 462. Cortot. Chopin, 2nd and 3rd Sonatas, Plus Encores, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 474. Klemperer, Bayerische Rundfunk Orchestra. Mendelssohn, Symphony No.3, 1969-05-23; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 486. Erich Kleiber. Japanese 78 Dubs, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 495 [195?]. Oistrakh, Radio Moscow Symphony Orchestra. Khatchaturian, Violin Concerto [Radio Moscow 09479], 1941; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
  - 519. Markevitch, Hungarian Radio and TV Symphony, Budapest Choir. Psalmus Hungaricus Rehearsal; Stravinsky, Symphony of Psalms; Kodaly, Psalmus Hungaricus; Brahms, Rhapsody; Ravel, Daphnis and Chloe. Budapest Music Week, 1965; 1 open reel tapes 9.5" reel in metal tin (Audio 30)
  - [10-626?] Standard Hour Programs, Hollywood Bowl. Stokowksi, Grainger, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 30)
- unnumbered tapes
  - Britten, Rostropovich. Aldeburgh Festival; Dods, BBC Concert Orchestra. Bax; Bliss, Ambrosian Singers. Bliss 1967; Lambert Recording of Rio Grande, 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 32)
  - Conducart 78 rpm Transfers, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Alfred Cortot, Pianist [ Victor 78s], 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 32)
  - Florence Desmond, 1 5" open reel tape folders (Audio 32)
  - Myra Hess, 1 5" open reel tape folders (Audio 32)
  - Jalas, World Symphony Orchestra. Sibelius Centennial, Hollywood Bowl, 1965-09-09; 1 3" open reel tapes folders (Audio 32)
  - Katims, NBC Symphony. Gillis, Symphony No.8 "Dance." rehearsal 10/20/49; performancce 10/22/49, 1949-10; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Landowska At Home (TV) 10/25/53; Conversation With Landowska At Intermission of 1949 Concert- Poulenc and Handel, 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 32)
  - Leinsdorf, RCA Italiana Opera Orchestra and Chorus. Madame Butterfly Act 1 and 2, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 32)
  - Los Angeles Philharmonic, 1965-03-04; 1 3" open reel tapes folders (Audio 32)
  - Mengelberg, Concertgebow Orchestra 3/21/43; M. Flipse, Bach Piano Concerto op.13 no.4 1/31/43; Jochum, Berlin Philharmonic 11/15/54, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Mitropoulos, NY Philharmonic. Ravel, L'Heure Espagnole; Rodzinski, NY Philharmonic. Shostakovich, 1950-11-26; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Monteux III. Monteux, Boston Symphony, Graffman. Stravinsky, Rachmaninoff, Tchaikovsky. Tanglewood, AM broadcast, 1961-08; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Munch, ORTF, Haskil. Mozart. Montreux 9/15/59; Kubelik, Orchestre de la Societe des Concertrs du Conservatoire, Haskil. Chopin 1/31/60; Schmidt, Bergmunster Studio Orchestra, Haskil; Kletzki, Orchestra Residence De La Haye, Haskil. Schumann 7/13/53; Desarzen, Lausanne Chamber Orchestra, Haskil. Mozart 6/25/56, 10/14/57, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 32)
  - Pardon My Blooper vol.1,3,5, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Piatigorsky, Barenboim. Mansion House, London [1991 rebroadcast], 1974-07-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 32)
  - Pollini, Vienna Philharmonic, Abbado. Brahms. Vienna 1976; Fischer. Schumann, Brahms, 1 5" open reel tape folders (Audio 32)
  - Reiner, Chicago Symphony Orchestra. Strauss, Ein Heldenleben [dub from RCA tape], 1954; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Scherchen, Hessian Radio Orchestra, Steverman. Schoenberg, Konzert Fur Klavier und Orchester op.42, 1955; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 32)
  - [Schoenberg,] Gurrelieder pts 3 and 4. sides 18-28, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Taming of the Shrew, 3 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 25)
  - Walter, NBC Orchestra, 1951-02-24; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Bruno Walter Demo Record 1, Copy of XLP15232, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Bruno Walter Rehearses Beethoven Columbia WZ-2, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Walter, Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1950; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
  - Henry Wood. Serenade to Music ;Glinka, 1 5" open reel tape folders (Audio 32)
  - Vivaldi Guardianship and Research in the Democratic Republic [Deutscher Demokratitischer Rundfunk, with cue sheets], 1978-03-27; 5 open reel tapes (stored as 9" pancake) (Audio 24)
  - [unidentified Japanese Sony Soni-Tape PW-5P], 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 32)
  - [unidentified Japanses Sony Aiwa Type 4], 1 5" open reel tape folders (Audio 32)
  - Rostropovich Tape. With Dedukhin 10/76; Bach Sonata. Soviet Record c.1955, 1 5" open reel tape folders (Audio 32)
  - unnumbered BBC Transcriptions from KPFA (From Finnie)
    - Aldeburgh. Debussy, Britten, Bach, 1961-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - Aldeburgh Festival 1959, Bach, Telemann, Dutilleux, Turina, Schubert, 1960-03-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - Edinburgh Festival. Rozhdestvensky, Leningrad Symphony Orchestra. Shostakovich, Miaskovsky, Tchaikovsky, 1961-03-23; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - Rostropovitch. Deduhin. Chopin, Shostakovich, 1960-02-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - Edinburgh Festival 1959. Baumgartner, Lucerne Festival Strings, 1960-03-26; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
    - Aldeburgh Festival, 1961-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
- 1. Handel, Concerto Grosso G Minor; Mozart, Symphony in G Minor [illegible, 3/3/50?], 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 32)
- 2. New York Philharmonic, 1950-02-02; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 32)
- 5. Rostropovich, Dedukhin. Brooklyn Academy of Music, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
- 9. Standard Hour Broadcast. Paulena Carter 5, 1950-05-21; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 32)
- 10. Toscanini, NBC Symphony. Haydn, Variations, 1950-05-24; 1 5" open reel tape (Audio 32)
- 24. Karajan, Los Angeles Philharmonic, 1954-07-02; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
- 45. Toscanini, NBC, Swarthout, Garris, Moscona. Berlioz, Romeo and Juliet 2/9, 16/47; The Great Interpreters - Busoni, Hofmann, Rachmaninoff BBC 9/16/72, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 55. Jochum, Los Angeles Philharmonic. Einem, Honegger, Strauss, Brahms, 1960-02-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 1)
- 66a. Southern California University. Program of Student Composers, 1960-05-16; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
- 87. Hollywood Bowl Concert Vol.1. Walter Hendl, Conductor. Berlioz, Le Corsaire Overture; Ives, Symphony No.2, 1960-08-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
- 88. Hollywood Bowl Concert Vol.2. Walter Hendl, Conductor. Leonard Pennario, Piano. Rachmaninoff, Piano Concerto No.2, 1960-08-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
- 89. Hollywood Bowl Concert Vol.2. Walter Hendl, Conductor. Respighi, Roman Festivals, 1960-08-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
- 94. Kempe, RPO, New Philharmonia Chorus. Brahms, Alto Rhapsody [RFH 27.674], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 95. Marigo, Glendale Symphony Orchestra. Gluck, Mendelssohn, Debussy, Copland, 1961-10-22; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
- 97. Abbado, Vienna Philharmonic. Bruckner, Symphony No.1 in C Minor; Kempe, Berlin Philharmonic. Dvorak, Symphony No.8 in G; Khaikin, Moscow Radio Orchestra. Glazounov, The Seasons [ASD 2522], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 104. Giulini, Boston Symphony. Brahms, Symphony no.4 11/7/69; Giulini, LA Philharmonic, Brendel. Brahms, Piano Concerto No.1. 1971, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 106. Schnabel, Piano. Mozart 1943; Szigeti. Beethoven, Mozart. Frick Museum 4/4/48; Szell, NY Philharmonic. Beethoven 6/17/45, Mozart 12/22/44, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 107. Schnabel, Piano. Walter, NY Philharmonic. Mozart 11/13/41; Wallenstein, LA Philharmonic. Mozart 1/13/46, Schumann 3/4/45; Rodzinski, NY Philharmonic. Mozart 3/3/46, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 114. Davis, Royal Opera House Covent Garden. Berlioz, Trojans, 1972-10-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 115. Davis, BBC Symphony. Berlioz, Benvenuto Cellini. Proms 7/24/72; Boult, BBC Symphony, Menuhin. Elgar, Violin Concerto in B Minor 8/16/72; Kempe, Munich Philharmonic. Haydn, Symphony No.7 3/9/74, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 119. Kempe, Munich Philharmonic. Prom 9/9/72; Mozart 3/9/74, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 120. Kempe, Munich Philharmonic. Mahler 9/10/72, Bruckner 9/11/72, 1972-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 137. Beecham, Chicago Symphony. TV Concert 3/1960; Giulini, Philadelphia Orchestra 3/21/69; Giulini Interview by R. Collier 3/72; Beecham, RPO, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 145. Kempe, Munich Philharmonic, Rothenberger. Strauss, Brahms, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 145 (2). Giulini, NY Philharmonic, Michelangeli 12/14/68; Giulini, Philadelphia Orchestra 3/3/72; Beecham, Seattle Symphony 2/18/60, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 156. Hollywood Bowl. Mehta, Los Angeles Philharmonic, Byron Janis, piano. Foss, Ode for Orchestra; Rachmaninoff, Concerto No.3; Berlioz, Symphonie Fantastique, 1961-08-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
- 157. Kempe, Swiss Festival Orchestra. Dvorak 1973; Boulez, BBC Symphony, Curzon. Mozart, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 158. Haitink, Concertgebouw. Bruckner. Prom 9/9/73; Kempe, Swiss Festival Orchestra, Peineman. Pfitzner 1/1/74, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 165. Giulini, Berlin Philharmonic. Mussorgsky, Tchaikovsky, Dvorak. West Berlin Radio, 1974-01-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- [175?] Pablo Casals, White House Concert; William Grant Still Ensemble, Mrs. W.G. Still, 1961-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
- 180. Kempe, BBC Symphony. Prom. Beethoven, Piano Concerto No.5 in E 8/30/74; Janacek, Sinfonietta 8/30/74, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 189. Urania Master Tapes, 1962-02-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 3)
- 193. Vox Master Tapes, 1962-02-23; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 195. Giulini, Boston Symphony Orchestra. Webern, Passacaglia, Op.1; Hindemith, Mathis Der Mahler; Bruckner, Symphony No.2, 1974-03-28; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 198. Decca Master Tapes, 1962-03-09; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 200. Giulini, Philadelphia Orchestra. Haydn, Debussy, Tchaikovsky ["Tape Defective"], 1973-05-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 207. Giulini, Vienna Symphony. Bruckner, Symphony No.2 in D. Vienna Festival 1974; Leppard, BBC Northern Symphony, Rostropovich. Strauss, Don Quixote 9/24/74, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 211. Waxman, L.A. Music Festival Orchestra, 1962-06-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 211 (2). Poole, LPO, BBC Chorus, Singers, Palmer. Brian, Symphony No.4, 1974-10-13; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 31)
- 212. Castro, L.A. Music Festival Orchestra, 1962-06-08; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 213. Walton, L.A. Music Festival Orchestra, 1962-06-10; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 214. Walton, Los Angeles Music Festival Orchestra, 1962-06-10; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 218. Hollywood Bowl. Steinberg, Johhanneson, 1962-07-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 224. Sibelius Festival, Helsinki, 1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 225. Sibelius Festival, Helsinki, 1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 230. Bernstein, New York Philharmonic [program enclosed], 1962-10-07; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 236. Bernstein, New York Philharmonic [program enclosed], 1962-10-14; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 237. Bernstein, New York Philharmonic [program enclosed], 1962-10-21; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 239. Bernstein, New York Philharmonic [program enclosed], 1962-10-28; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 241. Beecham, New York Philharmonic [program enclosed], 1962-11-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 243. Mehta, Los Angeles Philharmonic, 1962-11-15; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 244. Bohm, New York Philharmonic [program enclosed], 1962-11-18; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 245. Bohm, New York Philharmonic [program enclosed], 1962-11-25; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 257. Bernstein, New York Philharmonic [program enclosed], 1963-01-06; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 284. Klemperer, Philharmonia [crossed out, "Use 2126"], 1963-04-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 285. New York Philharmonic, Schippers April 6, April 13, 1963-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 287. English Recordings. Freccia, BBC Symphony; Ehrling, BBC Northern Orchestra, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 291. Bernstein, New York Philharmonic [program enclosed], 1963-04-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 296. Cayate, Los Angeles County Museum String Orchestra. Ysaye Memorial Concert, 1963-06-02; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 301. English Recordings. Robinson, BBC Northern Orchestra, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 313. Julliard String Quartet #1. Schnabel. Bartok Quartet No.3; Mozart, Concerto in B-flat, K.595, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 314. Julliard String Quartet #2. Mozart, Quintet k515; Schoenberg, Verklarte Nacht, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 318. English Recordings. Sir Henry J. Wood Proms Concerts. Del Mart, BBC Symphony. Mahler, 1963-08-26; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 323. Krips, New York Philharmonic. November 3, November 10., 1963-11; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 326. English Broadcasts. Reginald Tape. Norwich Municiple Orchestra. Haydn; del Mar, BBC Northern Orchestra. Neilson; Malcolm, BBC Chorus. Tallis, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 328. Mitropoulos, Minneapolis Symphony. Schnabel, Symphony. Wire Recording, Incomplete, 1946-12-12; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 329. Ormandy, Philadelphia Orchestra. Novemeber 24, December 29., 1963; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 330. Ormandy, Philadelphia Orchestra. JFK Memorial Concert. Bach; Beethoven; Dvorak, 1963-11-23; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 331. Kostelanetz, New York Philharmonic [program enclosed], 1962-12-29; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 332. Bernstein, New York Philharmonic. Avant-Garde Series. Xenakis, Pithoprakta; Ligeti, Atmospheres. January 5; Wolpe, Symphony No.1. January 19 [programs enclosed], 1964; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 335. Calderon, New York Philharmonic, Treger [program enclosed], 1964-02-02; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 4)
- 336. Ormandy, Philadelphia Orchestra. Ives, Three Places; Respighi, Church Windows, 1963-03-01; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 337. Susskind, Toronto Symphony, Oistrakh. Berlioz; Bach; Mendelssohn, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 343. Adler, Baltimore Symphony Orchestra, Gould. Strauss, Burlesque in D minor, 1962; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 350. Holland Festival No.1, 1963; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 351. Holland Festival No.2, 1963; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 352. City of Norwich Orchestra. Reginald Williamson Tape., 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 353. Henry Wood Promenades Concerts, 69th Season. Sargent, BBC Symphony, 1963-08-16; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 354. Henry Wood Promenades Concerts, 69th Season. Giulini, Philharmonia, 1963-08-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 358. Philharmonia. Roussel; Pijpen, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 359. BBC Transcription Service. Del Mar, London Symphony Orchestra and Chorus. Schoenberg, Gurrelieder, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 360. Kondrashin, Moscow Philharmonic Orchestra. Oistrakh, Menuhin, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 362. Furtwangler, Vienna Symphony Orchestra. Mozart, Beethoven; Mehta, Vienna Symphony Orchestra, Milstein. Salzburg Concert. Mozart, Brahms, 1963; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 364. Budapest Festival No.1, 1963; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 365. Budapest Festival No.2, 1963; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 366. Budapest Festival No.3, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 367. Budapest Festival No.4, 1963; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 368. Budapest Festival No.5, 1963; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 369. Budapest Festival No.6, 1963; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 370. Budapest Festival No.7, 1963; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 371. Budapest Festival No.8, 1963; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 373. Szell, Cleveland Orchestra. Walton; Vivaldi; Wagner; Sibelius, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 378. Music From Canada No.1. Sheiman, Canadian Broadcasting Corporation String Orchestra, Toronto, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 379. Music From Canada No.2. Montreal String Quartet. Gould, String Quartet, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 380. Malcolm, Philharmonia. Bach; Sviatislav Richter Recital, BBC, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 382. Net Television Concerts. Foss, Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra; Mitchell, National Symphony, Buswell 4/30/63; Szell, Cleveland Symphony, 1963-1964; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 384. Herrmann, CBS Orchestra, Farrell, Ness, Watson. Debussy, L'Enfant Prodique, 1947-10-05; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 386. Solomon, Columbus Philharmonic. Britten, Interludes from Peter Grimes, 1947-02-04; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 387. Furtwangler. Vienna Philharmonic; Berlin Philharmonic, 1942-03; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 387 (2). Furtwangler. Vienna Philharmonic; Berlin Philharmonic, 1942-1943; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 392. Stokowski, NBC Symphony. Schoenberg; Szell, Cleveland Orchestra. Schoenberg; University of Southern California Band. Schoenberg; Schillings, Berlin State Opera Orchestra. Strauss [Polydor 69742/2], 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)
- 393. Krips, Steinberg, New York Philharmonic, Casadesus, 1962-1963; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 5)